### About Me

I am a self-taught developer and product enthusiast. I have been programming for about 8 years, but my passion lies within building products. I use programming as a medium to create with a heavy focus on design. My objective is to find a career to further my experience in all aspects of product development and innovation.

# Experience

Angie's List Product Owner May 2014 - August 2014

As a product owner I led the initial development of a project to integrate Angie's List with a third party application. I worked mostly on visualizing the product, improving UX and working within the boundaries of the integration. This included writing stories for engineering to implement, storyboarding, and communicating with a team abroad.

#### Angie's List Software Engineer

May 2013 - December 2013

As a software engineer I worked within the Platform team to help transition Angie's List legacy .NET codebase to a more scalable high level architecture; utilizing new technologies and industry standards. I also documented and implemented integration testing within Angie's List applications to automate QA process for important feature sets.

#### Linechop LLC Co-Founder

June 2012 - August 2013

Co-Founded a startup company based in Chicago, a web service dealing with restaurant wait-list management. Developed a cloud based service that allowed for two way communication between restaurants and their customers.

#### PriceXperience Founder

December 2010 - January 2012

Developed 12 apps published to the Windows Phone Marketplace as well as web services that work alongside these apps (e.g. online leaderboards that track high scores).

## Technical Achievements

#### Indy Civic Hackathon June 2014

1st place Android app for detecting potholes. Developed back-end services to crowdsource pothole data into meaningful results.

#### Xtern Hackathon July 2014

2nd place Meteor app for location based messaging board. Access geographically defined areas only when within the boundaries.

#### Techweek Chicago June 2012

One of the 50 startups chosen to showcase at Techeek in Chicago. Received valuable feedback from leaders in the tech community.

### Education

Purdue University August 2010 - May 2016

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering

#### Core Courses

Data Structures & Algorithms, Advanced C Programming, ASIC Design, Microprocessors and Embedded Systems, Computer Design and Prototyping, Signals and Systems, Operating Systems

### Technical Skills

Javascript, HTML, CSS, Full-Stack Web Development, Meteor, Node, Express, ASP.NET, Python, Java, C, C#, SQL, MongoDB, RESTful Services, API's, Angular, React, jQuery, Django, Play Framework, Scala, Cordova, Microcontrollers, System Verilog, ASIC Design

### Other

References Contact Info upon request

Dual Citizenship (US/UK), 6 years of Spanish, member of Indy Xtern, Zeta Beta Tau, Verge Indy, Academic All State, Piano Product: Alex LaPrade Software Engineering: Roger Deetz